Thomas Leslie Crumrine III (Trey) Software Developer

Columbus Ohio | 614.557.5949 | tcrumrine51@gmail.com | linkedIn.com/in/yourname | Github link

SUMMARY

Quality and Customer focused Software Support Specialist transitioning into a Software Development role. Will graduate from an intensive coding bootcamp with a Certificate of Software Development. Built front-end and back-end web applications using full-stack C# .NET, MVC, Node.js, and other frameworks in April.

TECHNICAL AND TRANSFERABLE SKILLS

Computational Thinking Fundamentals ● Back-end Computer Programming/Object-Oriented Programming ● Front-end Web Development ● C# ● .NET ● REST API ● TDD ● Spring Boot ● Spring MVC ● JPA ● Scrum ● HTML ● CSS ● JavaScript ● Git ● React

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT PROJECT EXPERIENCE We Can Code IT

Planned, designed, and Interactive applications in collaborative, team-based, and independent settings demonstrating the proficiency to earn Software Development Certificate.

Virtual Pet

- Technologies used: C#
- Designed Virtual Pet that user can feed, play with, take to the vet, and interact with other pets.
- Enabled users to add pets to shelter and/or remove pets. And interact with multiple pets at once.

Class of Choice

- Technologies used: C#
- Designed a class for Football Players giving users the ability to create their own.
- Enabled users to select number, position, name, conference they wanted to play in or create their own team.

Computational thinking assignment

- Technologies used: C#
- Designed methods to determine answers to problems that users have prompted to them
- Enabled users to find out whether their nmbe ris even or add, if it is divisible by certain numbers, and even discover certain things about words they entered.

EDUCATION

We Can Code IT, City, State 2023

Certificate of Software Development

Columbus State Community College, Columbus, Ohio 2017

Attended 2 Years

WORK EXPERIENCE

Crumrine Financial Services

Insurance Agent, Westerville, Ohio

June 2022-January 2023

GitHub: https://TreyCrumrine..github.io

2023

- State Licensed to sell insurance in Ohio. Maintained License through continuing education.
- Sold Insurance polocies. Provided quality customer service to current customers to maintain clients.

Sears Heating and Cooling

Installer, Columbus, Ohio

September 2020-June 2022

- Licensed by the Enviormental Protection Agency for type II and II to respponsibly handle refrigerant.
- Replaced old furnace's and air conditioning units with new ones at customers request.

VOLUNTEER WORK: (Member of Dwell Community Fellowship. Volunteered with High School ministry from December 2017-June 2020)